dessy.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy | The Dessy Group

_Last Updated and Effective as of: June 19, 2018_

Your privacy is important to us. To explain how we respect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

The privacy policy below discloses the practices of The Dessy Group (“we”, “us”, “Company”) regarding information collection and use solely for the web site located at dessy.com (the "Web site"). This privacy policy does not apply to any other websites, apps or services provided by us, our affiliates or clients, unless it appears on such website, app or service.

This Web site is intended for use by the residents of the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, one of our sister sites may be more appropriate for your region:  

  * If you are situated in the European Economic Area, please use our European site at [https://de.dessy.com](https://de.dessy.com/),which is governed by our [European Privacy Policy](https://de.dessy.com/privacy/) and [Terms of Use](https://de.dessy.com/terms/).
  * If you are situated in the United Kingdom, Ireland or Australia, please use our UK site at [https://uk.dessy.com](https://uk.dessy.com/),which is governed by our [UK Privacy Policy](https://uk.dessy.com/privacy) and [Terms of Use](https://uk.dessy.com/terms/). 
  * If you are situated in Canada, please use our Canadian site at [https://ca.dessy.com](https://ca.dessy.com/), which is governed by our [Canadian Privacy Policy](https://ca.dessy.com/privacy/) and [Terms of Use](https://ca.dessy.com/terms/). 

By using or accessing or using the Web site, you signify your agreement to be bound by our Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SERVICE.

## Personal Information that we collect:

We do not collect personal information from you on the Web site unless you voluntarily provide it to us, such as by ordering a product, inquiring about a product, purchasing a product, using our chat service, registering to use a particular service or otherwise choosing to share your personal information with us. The personal information which you may provide to us could include your name, email address, physical address and payment information.

## Non-personal or Aggregate Information that we collect:

When you access our Web site, we may automatically collect non-personal information from you, such as referring web site, IP address, web pages viewed, browser type, usage and browsing habits on the Web site and similar data. We may also aggregate demographic information collected from our users (such as the number of users in a particular state) in a manner which does not identify any one individual.

## Information Usage, Disclosure and Recipients:

  * We may send your personal information to other group companies, affiliates and third parties to help us process your personal information for the purposes set out in this policy. 
  * We will only use your personal information as described below, unless you have specifically consented to another type of use, either at the time the personal information is collected from you or through some other form of consent from you:
  * We will use personal information to complete any orders you have placed.
  * We will use personal information to provide you with the specific services that you have requested, such as to reach a retailer.
  * We will use your personal information to respond to questions that you send to us.
  * We will use your personal information to send you emails from time to time, such as newsletters and notices about our promotions.
  * We may permit our vendors and subcontractors to access your personal information, but they are only permitted to do so in connection with performing services for us. They are not authorized by us to use the information for their own benefit. For instance, we may share your personal information with a credit card processing company or shipping provider to process orders that you have placed.
  * We may rent or sell your personal information to third parties for their own marketing purposes. If you would like to opt out of this, and you are a CA resident, please see the section title California Privacy.
  * We may disclose personal information as required by law or legal process.
  * We may disclose personal information to investigate suspected fraud, harassment or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, or the terms or policies for the Web site.
  * We may transfer your personal information in connection with the sale or merger of The Dessy Group or the division responsible for the services with which your personal information is associated.

Non-personal or aggregate information may be shared with any number of parties, provided that such information shall not specifically identify you.

We may receive data from other sources outside of your use of the Web site and combine that information with data collected from the Web site. When we do so, we will use the combined information as set forth in this privacy policy. 

## Interest Based Advertising:

We may ourselves, or with third party vendors, use non-personal information in connection with our own or vendor information to deliver targeted advertising to you when you visit other web sites or our Service. Cookies, clickstream data, and other similar technologies described below may be used in this process. For example, if you are searching for information on a particular product, we or our vendor may cause an advertisement to appear on other web sites you view with information on that product. This form of advertising, sometimes called “behavioral advertising,” is based on anonymous information and not on any personal information. As a result, we and our vendor know your interests, but do not personally identify you in connection with the delivery of that specific ad. We believe that such advertising is helpful because you will see advertisements that are relevant to your interests. However, if you would like to opt out of these interest-based advertisements, please follow the opt-out process described below under the section “Opt-Out Process”.

## Cross Device Matching:

We use non-personal information to facilitate cross device association. We or our third party vendors analyze device activity data using a mathematical tool known as a “probabilistic algorithm” to determine if you have interacted with content across multiple devices and to match such devices. In connection with this analysis, we may rely on non-personal information (including demographic, geographic and interest-based data) from third parties such as data vendors, pursuant to their own privacy policies or we may use the non-personal information we collect in conjunction with such third party data. Based on this data, we may then display targeted advertisements across devices that we believe are associated and may provide other services to our advertisers such as tools, analyses, data and insights to see how their web site or mobile applications are used and to further enable the display of targeted advertisements to you, including across your devices. Our advertisers may also provide us with deterministic data about you that may be used to supplement our probabilistic data. Based on this data, we may then display targeted advertisements across devices that we believe are associated and may provide other services to our advertisers such as tools, analyses, data and insights to see how their web site or mobile applications are used and to further enable cross-device targeting and analysis. For further instructions on restricting our use of certain cross-device data, please see the “Opt-Out Process” section below. Cookies and Similar Technologies: "Cookies" are pieces of information that may be placed on your computer by a web site for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with that web site. Many web sites use cookies for these purposes. We may use cookies (and similar items such as clear gifs, web beacons, tags, etc.) to customize your visit to the Web site and for other purposes to make your visit more convenient or to enable us to enhance our service. Such data may include, without limitation, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your device type, and general location data. In addition, we may also use and place cookies on your device from our third party service providers in connection with the Web site, such as an analytics provider that helps us manage and analyze Web site usage. Our advertisers and business partners may set cookies and similar items on your computer when you use our Web site. We may also use and place cookies on your device from our third party service providers in connection with the Web site, such as an analytics provider that helps us manage and analyze Web site usage. We use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. Our persistent cookie remains active on your hard drive for up to one (1) year. We set a persistent cookie to enable us to track and target the interests of users to enhance the services we provide. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use our Web site, but it may interfere with some of its functionality. Cookies and similar items are not used by us to automatically retrieve personal information from your computer without your knowledge. To stop, restrict or disable the placement of cookies, please see the “Opt Out Process” section below. 

## Clickstream Data:

As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each website you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as “clickstream data,” can be collected and stored by a website’s server. Clickstream data can tell us the type of device and browsing software you use and the address of the website from which you linked to the Service. We may collect and use clickstream data to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on websites, how visitors navigate throughout websites and how we may tailor our Service to better meet consumer needs. This information will be used to improve our Service and our services. Any collection or use of clickstream data will be anonymous, and will not intentionally contain any personal information.

## Security:

The security of your personal information is very important to us. We attempt to provide for the secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers by utilizing encryption software. However, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and The Dessy Group or information stored on the Web site or our servers, will be free from unauthorized access by third parties such as hackers and your use of the Web site demonstrates your assumption of this risk. We have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to perform their duties are authorized to have access to your personal information. For more information on protecting your privacy, please visit www.ftc.gov/privacy.

## Data Retention:

We will only retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements, to resolve disputes, and to enforce our agreements. Even if we delete some or all of your personal information, we may continue to retain and use anonymous or aggregated data previously collected. Please note that we will not be liable for disclosures of your data due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties.

## Third party links and social networking services:

This Web site may include links to third-party web sites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party web sites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our Web site, we encourage you to read the privacy policy of every web site you visit.

The Web site may integrate with social networking services. You understand that we do not control such services and are not liable for the manner in which they operate. While we may provide you with the ability to use such services in connection with our Website, we are doing so merely as an accommodation and, like you, are relying upon those third party services to operate properly and fairly.

You should be aware that personal information which you voluntarily include and transmit online in a publicly accessible blog, social network or otherwise online may be viewed and used by others. We are unable to control such uses of your personal information, and by using such services you assume the risk that the personal information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties.

## Your disclosures in publicly assessable forums:

You should be aware that personal information which you voluntarily include and transmit online in a publicly assessable blog, chat room, social media platform or otherwise online may be viewed and used by others without any restrictions. We are unable to control such uses of your personal information, and by using such services you assume the risk that the personal information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties for any number of purposes.

## Protection for Children:

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children.  When we become aware that personal information (or other information that is protected under applicable law) from a child under 13 (or such other age as may be restricted under local law) has been collected, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

## Other Web Sites:

As a convenience to you, we may provide links to third-party web sites from within the Web site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these third-party sites. When you link away from our Web site, you do so at your own risk.

## Style.Me Privacy Policy:

Details about our fit partner's privacy policy, Style.me, is available at <https://www.style.me/privacy>

## Communications with The Dessy Group:

By providing your email address to us, you expressly consent to receive emails from us. We may use email to communicate with you, to send information that you have requested or to send information about other products or services developed or provided by us, provided that, we will not give your email address to another party to promote their products or services directly to you without your consent.

You expressly agree that we are free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, or techniques contained in any communication you send to us without compensation and for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to, developing, manufacturing and marketing products and services using such information.

## Opt-Out Process:

_Opting out of messages from us_

All unsubscribe or opt-out requests should be sent to us at support@dessy.com and we will process your request within a reasonable time after receipt. 

_Opting out of cookies_

If you want to stop or restrict the placement of cookies or flush any cookies that may already be on your computer or device, please refer to and adjust your web browser preferences. Further information on cookies is available at www.allaboutcookies.org. By deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our Web site or some of its functionality may be affected. Cookies and similar items are not used by us to automatically retrieve personal information from your device without your knowledge. 

_Opting out of interest based advertising_

The online advertising industry provides a service through which you may opt-out of receiving targeted ads from certain data partners and other advertising partners that participate in self-regulatory programs. We comply with the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising set forth by the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA). You can opt-out of targeted advertising from certain providers at www.aboutads.info/consumers. Please note that by opting out, you will continue to see generic advertising that is not tailored to your specific interests and activities. To be clear, cookie-based opt-outs must be performed on each device and browser that you wish to have opted-out. For example, if you have opted out on your device browser, that opt-out will not be effective on your mobile device. You must separately opt out on each device. 

## California Privacy:

If you are a California resident this section applies to you. Under California Law, California residents have the right to request in writing from businesses with whom they have an established business relationship, (a) a list of the categories of personal information, such as name, email address and mailing address and the type of services provided to the customer that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes and (b) the names and addresses of all such third parties. To request the above information, please contact us at support@dessy.com. If you do not want your personal information shared with any third party who may use such information for direct marketing purposes, then you may opt out of such disclosures by sending an email to us at support@dessy.com. 

## Terms of Use:

Use of the Web site is also subject to our Terms of Use.

## United States of America:

Our Web site is maintained in the United States of America. If you are visiting from the regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from those in the United States, please note that you may be transferring your information to the United States and in other countries around the world. You freely and specifically give us your consent to export and use your information within the United States and in other countries as specified in this Privacy Policy. You understand that data stored in the United States may be subject to lawful requests by the courts or law enforcement authorities in the United States.

## Changes to policy:

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. However, if at any time in the future we plan to use personal information in a way that materially differs from this policy, we will post such changes here and provide you the opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. Your continued use of the Web site following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes.

For questions or concerns relating to privacy, we can be contacted at: support@dessy.com or 800-444-8304.

## The Dessy Group

8 West 38th Street  
4th Floor  
New York NY 10018
